export const ssc = [
  {
    isAttempted: false,
    finalScore: 0,
    questions: [
      {
        ques: 1,
        Question: "How many legs are in cockroach",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_2",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 2,
        Question: "Shape of Moon",
        a: "Round",
        b: "Oval",
        c: "square",
        d: "Flat",
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 3,
        Question: "Color of cow",
        a: "White",
        b: "Black & White",
        c: "Green",
        d: "Pink",
        ans: "option_2",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 4,
        Question: "How many legs are cockroach",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_2",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 5,
        Question: "How many fingers in human hand",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 6,
        Question: "Color of Sun",
        a: "Yellow",
        b: "Green",
        c: "Blue",
        d: "None",
        ans: "option_3",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 7,
        Question: "Color of Mars",
        a: "Red",
        b: "Green",
        c: "Blue",
        d: "None",
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 7,
        Question: "Color of Sky",
        a: "Yellow",
        b: "Green",
        c: "Blue",
        d: "None",
        ans: "option_3",
        curransers: "",
      },{
        ques: 8,
        Question: "How many fingers in human hand",
        a: 10,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },{
        ques: 9,
        Question: "Full form of HTML",
        a: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        b: "High Text Magnified Language",
        c: "High Time Machine Language",
        d: "Heavy Text Markup Language",
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },{
        ques: 10,
        Question: "How many legs in human ",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_3",
        curransers: "",
      }
    ]
   
  },
];
export const prog = [
  {
    isAttempted: false,
    finalScore: 0,
    questions: [
      {
        ques: 1,
        Question: "How many legs are in cockroach",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_2",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 2,
        Question: "Full form of HTML",
        a: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        b: "High Text Magnified Language",
        c: "High Time Machine Language",
        d: "Heavy Text Markup Language",
        ans: "option_1",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 3,
        Question: "Full form of css",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_3",
        curransers: "",
      },
      {
        ques: 4,
        Question: "How many legs have in cockroach",
        a: 5,
        b: 6,
        c: 2,
        d: 4,
        ans: "option_2",
        curransers: "",
      },
    ],
  },
];
